

Canberra, ACT, Australia.

#### **PROFILE**

I have developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake. As a graduate I have supervisory and information technology related experience across several industries. 14 years of provisional training, promoting lateral thinking and quick solution. Proficient in computer operation and professional communication. Comfortable learning new skills and applying existing experience to new task. Emphasis on professional collaboration and problem solving on time with excellence.

#### CONTACT

Phone: 0432809600

Email: rahmanmuhit19@gmail.com

#### **GITHUB:**

https://github.com/muhitrahman

## LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhit-rahman-2a3636165/

## **YOUTUBE:**

Channel under construction

## SYED MUHITUR RAHMAN

## **CURRENT DEVELOPMENT**

- Completed Front End and Back End bootcamp
- Completed Udemy MySQL database bootcamp
- Completed LCO web development Django bootcamp
- Completed Android development and Node.js bootcamp
- Studying HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Python, Database and Mobile Apps via online tutorials and side projects
- Connected with StackOverflow and another community
- Comfortable with GitHub
- Currently working on my independent projects

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## ICT Teacher, Moulvibazar International School Bangladesh --- May 2016 to August 2019

- Creates lesson plans that are appropriate for the age and abilities of the students in the class
- Assigns special projects to students
- Conducts research
- Run the classroom within the allocated budget and time

## Project Contributor and Students Assistant, Intech Institute of Technology

## Brisbane, Australia --- April 2015 to March 2016

- Contributed on skilling India project for Mindstorms EV3 robotics booklet
- Assist students with their study

# Assistant Manager, Oporto Brisbane, Australia --- January 2010 to March 2016

 Customer service, clean line safety, order placement, stock control, cash handling, everyday business update on system

Student Service Manager, Mentors education

#### **HOBBIES:**

Soccer Movies

#### Bangladesh--- 2008

- Handling students complain
- Customer service
- Bookkeeping student's data
- Business improvement

# Contractor, Water Supply and Sanitation, PHD, Bangladesh Govt. Bangladesh--- February 2003 to May 2007

• Water supply and sanitation for rural area development

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### 2014-2016

# Intech institute of Technology, Australia Advance diploma in computer system technology

 Software development, Networking, Cyber Security, Robotics

#### 2013-2014

## Canterbury Technical Institute, Australia Diploma in software development

• Software development, web development

#### 2011

## Captain Cook College, Australia

Certificate 3 in information technology

#### 2003

#### National University, Moulvibazar

Bachelor's degree in social science

#### 1999

## Dhaka State College, Dhaka

• Higher Secondary Certificate in Science

## 1996

## Patanusher High School, Moulvibazar

Secondary school certificate in science

#### PERSONAL SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Web development
- Object oriented languages (OOP)
- Windows server 2008R2 and Cisco routing
- software development methodology, Linux basics, ethical hacking, penetration, scanning, security
- VMware, Ubuntu, GNS3, PT
- Web design and mobile apps

#### **REFEREES**

#### Mr. Robin

Teacher, Intech Institute of Technology

Phone - +61422524728

## Mr. Steve

Teacher, Canterbury Technical Institute Phone - +61433178499

## Mr. Vic

Owner, Oporot, Brisbane Central Phone - 0730127822

## Mr. Sam Mura

Head Chef, Cosi Ristorante Italiano, Clayfield Phone - 07 3862 2160

## Thank you for your time and consideration